KANIDTHA KHAMNGAM

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Full name: Kanidtha Khamngam

Date of Birth: January 14, 2000

Age: 24 years

Nationality: Thai

CONTACT

+6690-399-8394

kanidtha.khamngam@gmail.com

www.github.com/kanidthafah

Chang Puek, Chiang Mai 50300

SKILLS

Programming Languages

- JavaScript
- TypeScript

Frameworks/Libraries

- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- React.jsNext.js

Language

- Thai (Native)
- English (Basic)

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree Chiang Mai University

2019-2023

College of Arts, Media and Technology

Modern Management and Information Technology

High School

Fangchanupathum School

2016-2018

Enrichment Program of Science Mathematics Technology and Environment (SMTE)

PROFILE

My name is Kanidtha. After I graduated from Chiang Mai University with a Bachelor of Science in Modern Management and Information Technology. I have enhanced my skills in Front End development through various online courses. I have also worked as a Front End Developer (Freelance Outsource) at Aquila Studio Company for three months.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer (Freelance Outsource)

Aquila Studio Company Limited

March 2024 - May 2024

- Developing and implementing UI components using Next.js, React.js with TypeScript and TailwindCSS
- Work with Back-end developers to integrate UI components with APIs and databases.
- Debug errors and troubleshoot issues.

Online marketing (Co-operative Education)

CMU Capricious

May 2022 - March 2023

- Planning the goals and objectives of a business using Business Model Canvas
- · Planning marketing strategy for sales increasing.
- Products photography and video, edit images and post them on Social Platform.
- Created content and promotions.

ABOUT PROJECTS

Portfolio Website Next.js, React.js and TailwndCSS

- This project is a Portfolio Website using React.js and Next.js, showcasing information about me, projects and skills
- Styled the website with Tailwind CSS to responsive design.
- Other tools/Libraries: Framer Motion, Shadon UI and SweetAlert2

eCommerce Website Next.js, React.js with TypeScript and TailwndCSS

- This project is an online e-commerce platform using Next.js and React.js with TypeScript.
- Responsive design with Tailwind CSS, ensuring an optimized shopping experience across devices
- Other tools/Libraries: Framer Motion, Shadon UI and React Toastify

Weather API Website HTML, CSS and JavaScript

- This project is a Weather API Website to display real-time weather information such as temperature, humidity, wind speed, etc.
- Using OpenWeatherMap API to fetch weather data based on user-input city queries.
- Handled API responses effectively, displaying error messages for invalid queries or unavailable data.

and other projects, please scan QR Code for see all my projects

